[KAZUMA] Hey! You think
you can just run out on us?
And then leave
behind a measly letter
saying, "goodbye?"
Sorry, but the three of us
refuse these terms!
[ALL] [chanting]
Darkness! Darkness!
I'm afraid
I must ask you all to go.
Milady's refusing
to see any visitors.
[gasps]
Oh, look...
this little bag here
just happened
to fall into your pocket.
Now then,
if you'll open up the gate
and quietly let us
through that would--
What? I am not a man
who takes bribes!
[KAZUMA] This note
doesn't tell us anything,
- dammit!
- [AQUA] Exactly!
So we demand an explanation
right now, understand?
[ALL] [chanting]
Darkness! Darkness!
[HAGEN]
Quickly! The guards!
Summon the guards at once!
- [all gasp]
- [ALL] Da...
[KAZUMA] We're gonna go
make lunch now!
So, you'd better
show up for it!
[KAZUMA] She's being
such a pain in the ass!
Fine I don't care!
Yeah, you can say
that all you want
but you're working
on a new product
- for her sake, aren't ya?
- [gasps]
You-You've gotta be
kiddin' me!
Hasn't it ever occurred
to you that
hoarding wealth is fun?
Whatever.
Word of advice,
a demonic prophecy
is almost always...
[KAZUMA]
I just don't want a real job!
[groans]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
If I give you some money,
will you head back home?
I have every right
to take part
in choosing our new member,
so that's what I plan to do.
[panting]
Abandoning someone
after overcoming
so much together?
You're a demon, Kazuma!
Demoniacal!
Would you gimme a break!
She's the one who told us
to find someone new.
Uh-huh?
Listen, when it comes
to endurance,
we totally suck
and you know it!
We need a tank, okay?
[birds chirping]
All I did was introduce myself.
You freaking sabotaged me!
My name is Megumin!
Regarded as Axel's
foremost wielder of magic,
and one who controls
Explosion magic!
You may have heard
of me, locally,
I'm often referred to as
"the crazy Explosion girl!"
Oh, crap, I have heard of her.
Sorry!
But, I'm not ready
to sign up for all this!
So, you'll have
to get somebody else!
Huh!
We actually found a guy
who was interested.
But, now?
These people won't even
make eye contact with us
after that damn
show you put on!
Oh, well, it is what it is.
Why don't we go home
for today, then?
You did that on purpose!
You were trying'
to make sure no one else...
[DUST]
Kazuma!
[KAZUMA]
Why are you in such a panic?
There's big trouble brewing
and I need your help!
[KAZUMA] This dude ran
head-first at a hydra,
and now he's this worked up?
♪
Sounds pretty serious!
I better go check it out!
This is about Rin
going out with some guy?
Yeah, that's right!
And I'm worried that
one of my good buddies
might be in the clutches
of a real creep!
[KAZUMA]
Okay, fair enough.
[DUST] Lately she hasn't really
been that social at all.
I got curious,
so I watched her
around the clock.
And she went
into an inn with some guy
- I didn't recognize!
- Hang on you're stalking--
I gotta look out
for my pal, right?
Please I need your help!
As vaguely creepy
as I find this I'll do it!
[chuckles] I knew
you'd understand, Kazuma!
Take this!
[DUST]
Here's the place.
It's where that scumbag
who's been tricking
Rin hides out.
You aren't just
gonna bust in, are ya?
Do you know how many years
I've been an adventurer?
You don't survive long
in this kinda job
unless you're always
fully prepared.
[gulps]
♪
The walls are thin here,
so be careful.
Sure, you're not stalking?
[NOBLE 09-A (M)] Oh, Miss Rin!
I cannot help the way
I truly feel!
- [RIN] Calm down!
- [both gasp]
A noble can't be
this infatuated
with an adventurer!
[NOBLE 09-A (M)]
I'm fully aware
of our different standings!
If nothing else,
then please let me
get a picture
with this magic camera!
[RIN]
Calm yourself!
You have to settle down!
Think clearly!
[KAZUMA]
I get it.
He knows the two of them
can never be together
so he wants a picture
to remember her by.
Sounds kinda reasonable to me?
[NOBLE 09-A (M)]
I want a lascivious one!
Something lewd
and salacious, if you please!
[KAZUMA]
Nope, that guy's a scumbag!
Well, that does it.
I've got an ass to kick.
Easy don't do this!
Simmer down!
[RIN] Just try and relax
for a minute! Okay?
We can go downstairs,
have some tea, and then we...
[NOBLE 09-A (M)]
I'm begging you!
Something bawdy
and titillating!
♪
He wasn't kidding.
Unbelievable.
I'll show him
what he can do with this crap!
Hey, if you mess up
the room then--
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
[groan]
[gasp]
♪
- [DUST] Kazuma.
- [KAZUMA] I'm Kazuma.
[DUST] You're gonna take
some pictures of me.
[KAZUMA]
Okay.
[DUST] We'll cover every bit
of that film with my flesh.
Giving that sleaze a whole
lifetime worth of trauma!
[whimpering]
[sighs]
♪
[KAZUMA]
All right.
Don't go getting
cold feet on me, now.
[DUST]
Of course not.
[KAZUMA]
Okay, you're fierce!
You're a tomcat!
[camera shutter clicking]
[camera shutter clicks]
♪
[KAZUMA] I don't even know
how many shots we took.
I just kept snapping away.
♪
Looking down at Dust
as I stood on a table.
Ground-level shots.
We were trying
every angle imaginable.
Okay, let's go for something
a little more impressive now!
Spread your legs,
drop your hips!
Good exactly like that!
[thuds]
- All ready to sumo!
[both laughing]
- [door opens]
- [gasps]
[laughing]
[both whimpering]
[RIN]
So, what the hell is this?
- [DUST] We're sorry.
- [KAZUMA] We're sorry.
[KAZUMA] Guess,
we got kinda carried away.
[sighs]
Why did I even
bother worrying, sir?
Well, you know what?
You can enjoy your trash.
- Kazuma, let's go.
- [gasps]
Are you sure leaving
them alone together is.
[RIN] I said, "let's go."
[NOBLE 09-A (M)]
I never expected
to see you here in my room.
What did you say?
Have you got
some kinda problem?
How perfect.
Let's have a little chat,
mano a mano?
[door shuts]
You'd better brace yourself.
Uh, Rin, shouldn't
we stop those two?
Things could get...
- [gasps]
- I really tried, ya know?
'Cause, I wanted
to make the effort.
And then he shows up,
in his room,
dressed like that?
It's like a duck jumping
head-first into boiling water
and closing up
the lid on the pot!
[whimpering]
Amazing! I never imagined I...
Hey, don't go thinking
I'm gonna be intimidated
because you're a noble!
This thing is nothing for me!
I'm used to dealing
with aristocrats and royals.
You are?
Then, this is the proof
that God is real!
I'm glad I converted,
so blessed.
You listen to me!
We're two dudes,
plain and simple.
And none of that
other stuff matters!
- Understand?
- [gasps]
Then you'd pay no mind
to our different status?
Oh, this is a day
that's truly blessed!
I am forever grateful.
Goddess Aqua be praised!
[grunts]
[RIN] Here's the thing,
Dust is the one
that noble likes.
Hang on. Say what?
I'm trying to tell you.
He has a major crush on Dust
and kept pestering me
for advice!
So I tried to talk him
out of it
while being as gentle
as possible
but then he asked to at least
get a picture of Dust.
If that's the case.
Dust must be...
- [screams]
- [gasps]
[KAZUMA]
Nothing happened today.
[RIN]
B-By the way, I heard about
another noble who...
You can stop right there!
Because I don't wanna hear it!
Relax this is something
totally different!
It's about Lalatina.
[KAZUMA]
Darkness?
Everyone in town's
talking about it.
Apparently, the daughter
of the Dustiness family
is getting married
to Aldarp pretty soon.
♪
[both gasp]
I want the details! Right now!
[AQUA]
Married?
Oh, I don't like this at all.
It's turning out just
like that shady demon said.
And you believe
the rumors are actually true?
Vanir didn't really give
a whole lot of specifics.
But one thing's for sure,
we know who's involved now,
so this is gonna
change everything!
We've gotta hear the full story
from Darkness, herself!
Don't we? Don't we?
- Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
[KAZUMA]
I can't believe it!
That girl's always been
a handful!
But with this news from Rin,
there's no choice.
We have to do something!
Our hands are tied!
All right, Aqua, hit me up.
Yeah, you got it!
Powered! Speed Gain!
Resist Magic!
And Versatile Entertainer too!
What was that last one?
It's to make you
a multi-threat talent!
Ow, ow! Seriously,
quit pulling!
You really intend
to do this alone?
Out of all of us,
my Lurk skill ought a
make me the safest bet.
You two head for the mansion
and wait for me.
Good luck.
I've got this!
[NORRIS]
It's so strange.
We didn't find anything,
Norris!
So, why don't we head
to the kitchen downstairs
and have 'em make us
some snacks?
Yeah, all right.
But I could've sworn
I heard something, earlier.
[KAZUMA]
Now, then...
where's Darkness?
What about the kitchen?
If she gets hungry,
then orders some food,
I could follow it back
to wherever her room is.
Ah but, that's a long shot.
Maybe if I could figure out
how to do some impressions.
♪
[NORRIS (KAZUMA)]
"My name's Norris
and I heard a strange noise."
[screams]
Wait a minute,
this is what she meant
by being
a "versatile entertainer?"
[DARKNESS (KAZUMA)]
"Kazuma, you are so amazing!
Take me!"
[KAZUMA] This is great
and it's gonna come in
so handy!
Aqua, I owe you an apology!
[knocking on door]
[MAID 09-A (F)] Miss,
I brought out your dinner.
[DARKNESS]
No, thank you.
[MAID 09-A (F)] But, Mr. Norris
said to prepare it and...
Please forgive me,
but I need rest.
[MAID 09-A (F)]
Yes, of course.
[NORRIS (KAZUMA)] Milady,
Kazuma Satou is here
and wishes to see you.
I told you not
to let him get through.
[DARKNESS]
Showing up at a time like this.
He is truly unbelievable, sometimes.
[NORRIS (KAZUMA)] But, Milady,
this "Kazuma" says that
if we refuse to allow him in
and meet with you in person,
he'll be forced to tell
the entire guild
your most embarrassing secrets.
That sounds like him.
Tell him he is free to.
I will never see
the guild again, anyway.
[NORRIS (KAZUMA)]
But, Milady, he mentioned that
you've been rather anxious over
how shredded your abs
are lately,
and that you should
simply cut down
on protein or something
to that effect.
[gasps]
Also, he said that
since you were holding up
that adorable dress,
and looking so happy
while doing so,
we should have one
prepared for you
as soon as possible.
[DARKNESS]
Th-Those are all lies!
Do not believe a word he says!
[NORRIS (KAZUMA)]
Actually, I'm afraid
he's made an even more
ridiculous claim.
Should I tell you?
[sighs]
Yes, go on.
[NORRIS (KAZUMA)]
You've been quite overcome
with physical longings
on a daily basis
and spend every night...
[screams]
[gasps]
Attack!
You'd better not think
I'm gonna go down
too easy with all
these awesome buffs
I've got right now!
[gasps]
♪
[whimpering]
Don't get me wrong!
I only came here
'cause I wanted us to talk.
Dammit!
Don't close your eyes
like you're surrendering!
Uh, knock it off, seriously!
Look, I'm gonna take
my hand away,
so don't scream, all right?
[muffled chuckle]
♪
[sighs]
Okay, here I go.
[DARKNESS]
Intruder!
[KAZUMA]
I knew it! This sucks!
What was I thinking?
I should've been way
more careful! Crap!
[NORRIS]
Miss Lalatina?
You are such a big faker!
[muffled grunt]
[GUARD 09-B (M)]
Are you all right?
We'll open this door
right now...
- [DARKNESS (KAZUMA)] Stay out!
- [gasp]
I am not presentable
at the moment!
I was playing, then things
became rather intense.
So I got carried away
and started shouting a bit!
Playing? I'm not sure
what you mean by playing!
An adult playing
by herself at this hour?
Must I spell it out
for you guys?
[muffled screams]
- [gasps]
- The rumors we've been hearing
- are actually true, then.
- Now, seriously!
[DARKNESS (KAZUMA)] Were you
perverts trying to see me doing
something dirty by claiming
to "check on my safety?"
[GUARD 09-B (M)]
Are you all right?
Y-Yes, I am fine!
I just forgot I had left
one of my indecent
magic toys on and that--
[screams]
[DARKNESS (KAZUMA)]
G-Gonna break!
I am losing my mind!
Any more
and I am coming apart! Ah!
[laughs]
[grunts]
- [sighs]
- I cannot believe you.
What are the servants
going to think of me now?
That I am impure and lewd?
[whimpering]
Eww, you just thought
about how much
you'd like that, right?
- [DARKNESS] I did not.
- [KAZUMA] You did, too!
[KAZUMA]
A debt?
[DARKNESS]
Indeed.
The daughter of a noble
is marrying the man
a debt is owed to.
It is that simple really.
[sighs]
You know of my proclivities,
do you not?
[chuckles]
I imagine I'm going
to pay for it physically,
without so much
as food or water.
Sounds exciting.
[KAZUMA]
You idiot.
If that was really true
you wouldn't look
as sad as you do right now.
♪
That's the reason
you wanted us
to take down the hydra.
Guess I screwed things up
by getting all those
people to help out.
[sighs]
So how much do you owe, exactly?
If you're short...
[DARKNESS]
Do not suggest paying, Kazuma.
I am a noble.
So the idea of letting
a citizen,
someone that
I am meant to protect,
repay my debts with his money.
I would rather be married off.
♪
[sighs]
[gasps]
♪
[DARKNESS]
So, you see...
if the alternative is letting
that lord have it. -[whimpers]
[moaning]
Hmm.
♪
[DARKNESS]
Say, Kazuma.
[KAZUMA]
I'm Kazuma
Maybe...
Maybe we could just...
♪
D-Darkness.
Your...
[gasps]
Your abs really are shredded.
[screams]
That was my fault
and I'm so sorry!
Things got too serious
and I couldn't take it!
Even I can lose my patience,
occasionally!
I braced myself, and you...
You are dead meat!
Oh, crap! What the
hell's going on here?
You actually do like me?
So why don't you just come out
and admit it then, Milady?
[DARKNESS] Who could ever love
an imbecile like you?
Certainly not me!
And do not call me "Milady!"
[GUARD 09-B (M)]
Milady, we're coming in!
Do not come in here, understand?
Lalatina is naked right now!
- So go away!
- [gasps]
My apologies, uh!
You have got to stop!
Do not ever use
my voice like that!
Hey, the intruder is in here
and using a skill
to mimic my voice!
[GUARD 09-B (M)]
What, here we come!
Okay, that's it!
Create Earth!
[all growling]
Close your eyes!
And Wind Breath!
[groans]
[KAZUMA]
Now, Lurk.
[GUARD 09-B (M)]
Don't let him escape!
Kazuma, come out
and I will let you off
with ten punches to the face!
But if I manage
to find you first,
it will be a thousand
times worse!
I promise you!
[KAZUMA]
This is bad.
Really bad. Let's go.
♪
Okay.
Out through the window.
[IGNIS]
Hello, is someone there?
[gasps]
♪
Oh, I didn't realize
it was you.
What brings you here
at this time of night?
Uh, well, I uh...
Ah, yes. I see.
It appears that
my daughter has been
blessed with good friends.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] That guy was a pillar
of this kingdom for a reason.
It's obvious to him
why I'm here.
Hate to spring this on ya
when you're not feeling good
but your daughter's lost
her damn mind.
So, could you talk
some sense into her?
[IGNIS]
If nothing else, I suppose it
would help to explain
why she's been keeping
to herself so much lately.
[KAZUMA] I'm serious, man.
This isn't funny.
♪
She said something
about being in debt.
But, I have a hard time
believing
you'd owe anything
to a scumbag like that.
Well... it seems you have quite
a good head on your shoulders,
Kazuma, my boy.
Perhaps I should
consider entrusting you
with my daughter, after all.
Huh?
Could I ask you
to take her and go
as far away
from this place as possible?
[KAZUMA] Really? I asked
about a debt and all of sudden
you want me to elope with her?
I'm sorry, but no thank you!
No, thank you
very much, in fact!
For your information
your crazy ass daughter's
the one who chased me in here!
[laughs]
[IGNIS]
Kazuma.
I'd appreciate you
not asking for details.
That said, after you have taken
her out of this place,
I will simply need to sell
the mansion off and...
[coughs]
W-What do you need help with?
Because we've got
an arch priest
whose only real value
is her power to heal.
Thank you,
but that kind of magic
has no effect on illness.
And the Resurrection spell
cannot be used
on somebody
who's died of natural causes.
Diseases are just
a part of living.
When one meets
their natural end
no divine miracle
can change that.
[sighs]
Which is why
you needn't look so sad.
[DARKNESS]
Kazuma, get out here!
You will regret ever
mimicking my voice!
[laughs]
Young man,
please look after my girl.
[KAZUMA]
But I really don't wanna.
[door thud open]
Found you!
It is time you are dealt
with properly!
Come on, would you mind
keeping it down a little bit?
[DARKNESS]
Enough out of you!
For being worried about me,
you have managed
to thoroughly sabotage
my reputation
in a single night!
Sorry, but everything
I said was true!
Yet another lie!
Screw this stupid
debt of yours!
Why don't we just
get outta this place?
Besides, it's not like
Aqua and Megumin
are gonna end this
if I come back alone!
Who knows?
Megumin
might explode
the wedding reception!
And if such a thing
were to happen
you would all end up hanging!
So, it is your job
to stop those two!
You have gotta be
the most stubborn
pile of girl muscle
I've ever met!
[growls]
♪
I won't run away!
If I chose to someone
else would suffer.
[grunts]
Yeah, ya know what?
Suit yourself then.
But if you ever get
a clue and want some help,
you know where the mansion is.
You can start with,
"Please, Kazuma, I need you!"
- [thuds]
- [groans]
[KAZUMA]
Strong window.
[glass shatters]
Oh, my goodness!
Are you all right, Kazuma?
♪
Y-You know,
if you ask really nicely,
we can make sure
that you receive treatment
after such an awful fall.
Who needs this crap?
Know what?
I'm not coming' back
to save you
till you come crying
for my help!
Dumbass! Dumbass!
- [screams]
- [thuds]
That didn't even hurt!
Okay.
[both snoring]
[door thud open]
[whimpering]
[KAZUMA]
Aqua!
I need healing!
I need healing! Please!
[VERDIA]
This is Verdia,
general
of the Devil King's army.
And I wanted to write
to you on behalf
of our esteemed organization.
Miss Lalatina Dustiness...